Class of 1988 Records, 1984-[ongoing]
Smith College Archives
Class of 1988 Records
1984-[ongoing]
Smith College. Class of 1988.
RG 80 UUID:bba533e6-74cb-4fab-80da-9d6a648c5268
4 boxes (1.5 linear ft.)
Smith College Archives Northampton, MA
This collection contains photographs, invitations, songs, newspaper clippings, and other memorabilia from the commencement and reunions of the Class of 1988.
The Class of 1988 was the 110th graduating class of Smith College.
The Class of 1988 Records contain materials describing the history and activities of the Class of 1988, including materials from commencement, reunions, and other important events. Types of materials include photographs, invitations, songs, newspaper clippings, programs, letters, and other memorabilia.
Individual biographical files are also available, and often include photographs, photo albums, newspaper clippings, letters and correspondences, and class notes.
Information on Use
Terms of Access and Use
The records are open for research according to the regulations of the Smith College Archives without any additional restrictions.
History of the Collection
The Class of 1988 Records were created by the students and donated to the College Archives.
- Commencement 1988 (Box 2296, Folder 1)
- Commencement Photographs 1988 (Box 2296, Folder 2)
- Freshman Record 1984-1985 (Box 2296, Folder 3)
- Groups 1984-1988 (Box 2296, Folder 4)
- Ivy Day 1988 (Box 2296, Folder 5)
- Junior Ushers 1987 (Box 2296, Folder 6)
- Last Chapel 1988 (Box 2296, Folder 7)
- Newsletter 2005 (Box 2296, Folder 8)
- Sophomore Push 1986 (Box 2296, Folder 9)
- 10th Reunion 1998 (Box 2296, Folder 10)
- Individuals A-D (Box 2296)
- Individuals E-N (Box 2297)
- Individuals O-Z (Box 2298)